{
    "subject": "resource/Tamara_(2005_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Katie_Stuart",
    "human_readable": "Tamara (2005 film) stars Katie Stuart.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8836464881896973,
            "question": "Is there a movie titled Tamara from 2005?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7887049913406372,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7350347638130188,
            "question": "Who directed the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6521599292755127,
            "question": "What is the name of the actress who starred in the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6012005805969238,
            "question": "What year was the film Tamara released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.585186779499054,
            "question": "What genre is the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5638534426689148,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5306321978569031,
            "question": "Was the film Tamara a success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46061262488365173,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the movie Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4469006359577179,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to the film Tamara?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tamara (2005 film) stars Katie Stuart.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3811_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the movie Tamara?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3811_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was the film Tamara a success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3811_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of the film Tamara?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3811_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3811_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that the 2005 horror film \"Tamara\" stars Katie Stuart. This information can be found in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3811/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt, which mentions \"Tamara is a 2005 horror film directed by Jeremy Haft and starring Jenna Dewan, Katie Stuart and Chad Faust.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the cast of the 2005 horror film \"Tamara\" includes Katie Stuart. Therefore, the statement \"Tamara (2005 film) stars Katie Stuart\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}